Ezz Elden Mohamed

El Mansoura , El Dakahleya | 01002368023 , 01552282922 | ezzelden4work@gmail.com

My WebSite, linkedin , codepen , GitHub

Front-end Web Developer

I'm a student in the Delta Academy, I study at the faculty of Management Information Systems. However, I'm a front-end web developer. I have 3 years of experience in this field. You can say that I'm a full-time Web developer in addition to being a student. I'm passionate about keeping up with everything new in technology trends, I have my personal touch at my work. you can be keen on me for any project you need to do.

Skills

Html | css | Javascript | jQuery | BootStrap | React js | Sass | GitHub | Css Animation | Adobe XD | Figma | React Native

Professional Experience

<u>Atheltree</u> 2020 - Present

• Front-end Web Developer

The Lean 2020 - 2020

- Front-end Web Developer
- Front-end Team Leader
- Project Operator

Afro Arab Digital 2020 - 2020

- Front-end Web Developer
- Front-end Team Leader
- Project Operator

<u>Devolum</u> 2018 - 2020

• Front-end Web Developer

Projects

Vuesax Dashboard

gitHub Live View

- Chart Plugin
- Dark & Light Mode
- Chat Page

Education

I'm a student in the Delta Academy

Langues

Arabic : Native | English : Good Write and Speak